<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dick grayson on Batfam Shitposts</title>
    <link>https://moosefrog.com/tags/dick-grayson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dick grayson on Batfam Shitposts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moosefrog.com/tags/dick-grayson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>002 - Abba</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/002/</guid>
      <description>G*d help the Bat-family when Damian Wayne discovers ABBA… and loves it.
OH gawd. I can’t get the image of Bat!Dick and Robin!Damian prepping for a night of patrol to ABBA. Dick would be dancing. Damian would be disparaging.
Until one evening, Dick catches Damian mouthing the words to Waterloo under his breath.
Dick can’t stop smiling ALL NIGHT and it irritates the heck out of Damian who will insist the song is terrible because of its historical inaccuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>005 - A Major Crush</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/005/</guid>
      <description>Dick: Uh-ohhhh, I think our little brother has a major crush on someone!
Jason: Mm? Is she hot?
Dick: I think you mean, is HE hot? Look at Damian&amp;rsquo;s sketchbook.
Jason flips through: Tall, dark, and handsome.. hm..
Tim: That&amp;rsquo;s John Wick.
Dick: Oh! You know him?
Jason: Who?
Tim: sighs He&amp;rsquo;s a character from a movie. He&amp;rsquo;s an assassin who goes on a killing spree when someone murders his puppy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>006 - Honey Badger</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/006/</guid>
      <description>Damian: I have decided to give the name Robin back to Drake.
Bruce: Oh? I thought you wer—
Damian: Father, please. I am now Honey Badger. An animal that more closely aligns with who I am.
Jason: Oooh yeah, fuck. I can see it.
Tim: I can’t unsee it.
Bruce: facepalms
Dick: Like… the video?
Damian: Yes.
Honey Badger Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>009 - Duck Season</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/009/</guid>
      <description>Damian: Good morning, Grayson.
Damian: Drake.
Tim: SERIOUSLY? I SHOULD&amp;rsquo;VE KNOWN YOU&amp;rsquo;D ATTACK MY NEW NAME LIKE THAT DAMIAN! AUGH! EVERYONE IS GIVING ME SUCH A HARD TIME! I THOUGHT I&amp;rsquo;D BE SAFE HERE FOR A FEW DAYS BUT NOOOOO storms out of the kitchen
Dick: head in hands Noooooo&amp;hellip; he was finally calm.
Damian: blink blink Since when is &amp;lsquo;Drake&amp;rsquo; a new name?
Jason: walks into the kitchen loading a tranq gun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>011 - Halloween</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/011/</guid>
      <description>Damian: I fail to see the point of this exercise, Grayson.
Dick: It&amp;rsquo;s Halloween, little D! Time to put on a costume, scare people and get candy!
Damian: looks down at his Robin costume
Damian: thinks about the last group of bad guys who screamed when they realized it was Robin, and not Batman, who was apprehending them
Damian: Hm. Gimme candy.
Dick: Ha ha, it&amp;rsquo;s not that ea—
Damian: hood goes up, evil smile is seen, a sword is drawn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>014 - Halloween Take Two</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/014/</guid>
      <description>Dick: That is NOT funny, you two.
Jason: Uh-oh, Damian. Dickybird has the grumps!
Damian: I agree, Grayson. This isn&amp;rsquo;t funny, it&amp;rsquo;s scary. As per your instructions.
Dick: You two dressing up as ZOMBIES for Halloween is just&amp;hellip; tasteless!
Jason: Boo. Hoo. Hoo. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s very hurtful to use the word &amp;lsquo;zombie&amp;rsquo;. Technically, we&amp;rsquo;re, what? Re-animated corpses?
Damian: Mm. I&amp;rsquo;m unfamiliar with the correct terminology.
Jason: C&amp;rsquo;mon, Damian! You lived with a guy who constantly got brought back from the dead, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>017 - Cycles</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/017/</guid>
      <description>Jason: rushes into the media room and shuts the door, leaning heavily on it Fuck! Guys! It&amp;rsquo;s happened!
Tim: Congratulations. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll make a great father.
Jason: What? No! No, it&amp;rsquo;s worse. They&amp;rsquo;ve synced!
Dick: Um, what?
Damian: Tt. Clearly Jason is referring to the menstruation cycles of the women in this household.
Everyone: stares at Damian who pulls out his smart phone
Damian: I&amp;rsquo;ve been tracking their cycles for months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>018 - Welcome Home</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/018/</guid>
      <description>Dick: Tim! You brought your bags! Are you staying at the Manor? Here, let me help you with that it looks heavy!
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Tim: Meh. I sorta got shot up and Alfred said he&amp;rsquo;ll worry himself into an early grave if I&amp;rsquo;m not here where he can keep an eye on me.
Dick: Haha! That sounds like Alfred, alright.
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Tim: And I heard Damian has laryngitis so it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to visit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>020 - Untitled Batfam</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/020/</guid>
      <description>Jason: Steal his keys!
Damian: Haha! Then honk until he gets confused!
Tim: No! I&amp;rsquo;m putting his keys in the pond! Ha! No more keys for joo!
Damian: HAHA YES! YES! No more keys for you, oppressive gardener!
Jason: Gimme a turn, Nerd boy!
Tim: Nuh-uh, you know the rule! I play until I die then someone else gets to play!
Damian: Yes, Todd, that is the rule we all agreed to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
