<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>damian wayne on Batfam Shitposts</title>
    <link>https://moosefrog.com/tags/damian-wayne/</link>
    <description>Recent content in damian wayne on Batfam Shitposts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moosefrog.com/tags/damian-wayne/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>002 - Abba</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/002/</guid>
      <description>G*d help the Bat-family when Damian Wayne discovers ABBA… and loves it.
OH gawd. I can’t get the image of Bat!Dick and Robin!Damian prepping for a night of patrol to ABBA. Dick would be dancing. Damian would be disparaging.
Until one evening, Dick catches Damian mouthing the words to Waterloo under his breath.
Dick can’t stop smiling ALL NIGHT and it irritates the heck out of Damian who will insist the song is terrible because of its historical inaccuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>003 - Organs</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/003/</guid>
      <description>I’m reading some canon Bat-comics and…
..holy fucking shit on a stick!
Did Talia SERIOUSLY replace every single organ in 10-year-old Damian’s body after he was in an explosion? Like, WITH NO MEDICAL EXAM FIRST?
Just straight up, yo, my boy’s doing good so like, let’s take him to the next level. Naw, don’t bother fixing any of those damaged organs, let’s just yank ‘em all out and put new ones in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>004 - Primary Lesson</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/004/</guid>
      <description>Damian: Drake, this is the third week in a row you have selected The Emperor&amp;rsquo;s New Groove as the movie night feature.
Tim: AND YET the primary lesson in this movie HAS YET TO BE ABSORBED!
Dick: Tim&amp;hellip;
Damian: Tt. The LESSON is very simple; do not entrust servants with important tasks. Duh. I had learned that lesson when I was three.
Jason: Dick! DICK! HELP ME RESTRAIN TIM! HE&amp;rsquo;S STRONGER THAN HE LOOKS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>005 - A Major Crush</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/005/</guid>
      <description>Dick: Uh-ohhhh, I think our little brother has a major crush on someone!
Jason: Mm? Is she hot?
Dick: I think you mean, is HE hot? Look at Damian&amp;rsquo;s sketchbook.
Jason flips through: Tall, dark, and handsome.. hm..
Tim: That&amp;rsquo;s John Wick.
Dick: Oh! You know him?
Jason: Who?
Tim: sighs He&amp;rsquo;s a character from a movie. He&amp;rsquo;s an assassin who goes on a killing spree when someone murders his puppy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>006 - Honey Badger</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/006/</guid>
      <description>Damian: I have decided to give the name Robin back to Drake.
Bruce: Oh? I thought you wer—
Damian: Father, please. I am now Honey Badger. An animal that more closely aligns with who I am.
Jason: Oooh yeah, fuck. I can see it.
Tim: I can’t unsee it.
Bruce: facepalms
Dick: Like… the video?
Damian: Yes.
Honey Badger Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>007 - Tactical Undergarments</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/007/</guid>
      <description>Jason: Hold up, I gotta take a piss.
Damian: This is very unprofessional, Hood.
Jason: pissing up against a chimney What? You don’t ever have to go when you’re on patrol?
Damian: Tt. I have adopted Father’s teachings.
Jason: shaking off You hold it? That’s not healthy for your kidneys.
Damian: making an EW face You don’t clean your hands afterwards? That is unsanitary. And no, I don’t hold it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>009 - Duck Season</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/009/</guid>
      <description>Damian: Good morning, Grayson.
Damian: Drake.
Tim: SERIOUSLY? I SHOULD&amp;rsquo;VE KNOWN YOU&amp;rsquo;D ATTACK MY NEW NAME LIKE THAT DAMIAN! AUGH! EVERYONE IS GIVING ME SUCH A HARD TIME! I THOUGHT I&amp;rsquo;D BE SAFE HERE FOR A FEW DAYS BUT NOOOOO storms out of the kitchen
Dick: head in hands Noooooo&amp;hellip; he was finally calm.
Damian: blink blink Since when is &amp;lsquo;Drake&amp;rsquo; a new name?
Jason: walks into the kitchen loading a tranq gun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010 - Duck Season II</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/010/</guid>
      <description>Damian: So&amp;hellip; Drake, is it?
Tim: Yes. And I&amp;rsquo;m keeping it. Fuck the haters.
Damian: I can respect that sentiment.
Tim: Thanks.
Damian: Did you know ducks are an excellent example of a species with intense sexual competition doing strange things to genitalia? Male ducks have penises that can reach three feet in length. I saw a picture of a duck with this twisted, knotted length of venous tissue dangling behind it and thought it was his intestines so remarkable is the resemblance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>011 - Halloween</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/011/</guid>
      <description>Damian: I fail to see the point of this exercise, Grayson.
Dick: It&amp;rsquo;s Halloween, little D! Time to put on a costume, scare people and get candy!
Damian: looks down at his Robin costume
Damian: thinks about the last group of bad guys who screamed when they realized it was Robin, and not Batman, who was apprehending them
Damian: Hm. Gimme candy.
Dick: Ha ha, it&amp;rsquo;s not that ea—
Damian: hood goes up, evil smile is seen, a sword is drawn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>012 - Graduation</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/012/</guid>
      <description>Damian: What do you mean you, &amp;ldquo;have the same teacher as last year&amp;rdquo;? I thought you had graduated?
Jon: Yeah, well, I guess Mrs. Johnson is teaching high school now. sigh She hates me.
Damian: has the strangest look on his face
Jon: Damian?
Damian: It&amp;rsquo;s nothing. So, tell me about your classes&amp;hellip;
[ Later ]
Damian: Hey, Todd. When boring regular American children graduate do they, or do they not, ritualistically shoot their teacher in the head and display the corpse in a corpse garden upon which they may gaze and appreciate the sacrifices that had been made to make them great?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>013 - Sharing is Caring</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/013/</guid>
      <description>Jason: Hey small-fry, what&amp;rsquo;re you eating?
Damian: Using a knife and fork Burger.
Jason: I thought you were vegetarian cuz of your pet cow?
Damian: I am. This is a &amp;lsquo;beyond meat&amp;rsquo; burger.
Jason: &amp;lsquo;Beyond meat&amp;rsquo;? Like, human flesh made in a laboratory soylent green-type meat?
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Jason: Here, if you&amp;rsquo;re grossed out, I&amp;rsquo;ll just finish that burger for you&amp;hellip;
Damian: smacks Jay&amp;rsquo;s knuckles with the back of his fork</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>014 - Halloween Take Two</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/014/</guid>
      <description>Dick: That is NOT funny, you two.
Jason: Uh-oh, Damian. Dickybird has the grumps!
Damian: I agree, Grayson. This isn&amp;rsquo;t funny, it&amp;rsquo;s scary. As per your instructions.
Dick: You two dressing up as ZOMBIES for Halloween is just&amp;hellip; tasteless!
Jason: Boo. Hoo. Hoo. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s very hurtful to use the word &amp;lsquo;zombie&amp;rsquo;. Technically, we&amp;rsquo;re, what? Re-animated corpses?
Damian: Mm. I&amp;rsquo;m unfamiliar with the correct terminology.
Jason: C&amp;rsquo;mon, Damian! You lived with a guy who constantly got brought back from the dead, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>015 - Halloween Take Three</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/015/</guid>
      <description>Damian: What? Are you wearing?
Steph: A costume!
Damian: You&amp;rsquo;re not going out on patrol with me like that.
Steph: You&amp;rsquo;re not my supervisor! :D
Damian: Father!
Bruce: If she wants to wear a sheet with two holes cut out of it over her regular costume, that&amp;rsquo;s on her.
Damian: Ugh.
Steph: It&amp;rsquo;s my Robin #2 costume! :D
Bruce: Wow. You come into my cave—
Steph: Jay gave me permission!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>016 - Halloween Take Four</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/016/</guid>
      <description>Damian: There. My costume is complete.
Jon: You&amp;rsquo;re wearing one of my outfits&amp;hellip; and a pair of my glasses?
Damian: Yes. I&amp;rsquo;m going as you. adjusts the glasses
Jon: Hmph. You&amp;rsquo;re hair&amp;rsquo;s not messy enough. Here&amp;hellip; let me&amp;hellip; *RUFFLE RUFFLE MUSS MUSS &amp;gt;:D *
Damian: hiss splutter slappy of hands away from his head Stop that!
Jon: awed voice It.. It&amp;rsquo;s springing back into shape! It&amp;rsquo;s like I didn&amp;rsquo;t even mess it up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>017 - Cycles</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/017/</guid>
      <description>Jason: rushes into the media room and shuts the door, leaning heavily on it Fuck! Guys! It&amp;rsquo;s happened!
Tim: Congratulations. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll make a great father.
Jason: What? No! No, it&amp;rsquo;s worse. They&amp;rsquo;ve synced!
Dick: Um, what?
Damian: Tt. Clearly Jason is referring to the menstruation cycles of the women in this household.
Everyone: stares at Damian who pulls out his smart phone
Damian: I&amp;rsquo;ve been tracking their cycles for months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>018 - Welcome Home</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/018/</guid>
      <description>Dick: Tim! You brought your bags! Are you staying at the Manor? Here, let me help you with that it looks heavy!
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Tim: Meh. I sorta got shot up and Alfred said he&amp;rsquo;ll worry himself into an early grave if I&amp;rsquo;m not here where he can keep an eye on me.
Dick: Haha! That sounds like Alfred, alright.
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Tim: And I heard Damian has laryngitis so it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to visit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>020 - Untitled Batfam</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/020/</guid>
      <description>Jason: Steal his keys!
Damian: Haha! Then honk until he gets confused!
Tim: No! I&amp;rsquo;m putting his keys in the pond! Ha! No more keys for joo!
Damian: HAHA YES! YES! No more keys for you, oppressive gardener!
Jason: Gimme a turn, Nerd boy!
Tim: Nuh-uh, you know the rule! I play until I die then someone else gets to play!
Damian: Yes, Todd, that is the rule we all agreed to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
