<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tim drake on Batfam Shitposts</title>
    <link>https://moosefrog.com/tags/tim-drake/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tim drake on Batfam Shitposts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moosefrog.com/tags/tim-drake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>004 - Primary Lesson</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/004/</guid>
      <description>Damian: Drake, this is the third week in a row you have selected The Emperor&amp;rsquo;s New Groove as the movie night feature.
Tim: AND YET the primary lesson in this movie HAS YET TO BE ABSORBED!
Dick: Tim&amp;hellip;
Damian: Tt. The LESSON is very simple; do not entrust servants with important tasks. Duh. I had learned that lesson when I was three.
Jason: Dick! DICK! HELP ME RESTRAIN TIM! HE&amp;rsquo;S STRONGER THAN HE LOOKS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>005 - A Major Crush</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/005/</guid>
      <description>Dick: Uh-ohhhh, I think our little brother has a major crush on someone!
Jason: Mm? Is she hot?
Dick: I think you mean, is HE hot? Look at Damian&amp;rsquo;s sketchbook.
Jason flips through: Tall, dark, and handsome.. hm..
Tim: That&amp;rsquo;s John Wick.
Dick: Oh! You know him?
Jason: Who?
Tim: sighs He&amp;rsquo;s a character from a movie. He&amp;rsquo;s an assassin who goes on a killing spree when someone murders his puppy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>006 - Honey Badger</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/006/</guid>
      <description>Damian: I have decided to give the name Robin back to Drake.
Bruce: Oh? I thought you wer—
Damian: Father, please. I am now Honey Badger. An animal that more closely aligns with who I am.
Jason: Oooh yeah, fuck. I can see it.
Tim: I can’t unsee it.
Bruce: facepalms
Dick: Like… the video?
Damian: Yes.
Honey Badger Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>008 - Sparking Joy</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/008/</guid>
      <description>Tim: pushing a pile of weapons off of the sofa so he can sit down Jay, you have way too many guns for a studio apartment.
Jason: Fuck you they spark joy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>009 - Duck Season</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/009/</guid>
      <description>Damian: Good morning, Grayson.
Damian: Drake.
Tim: SERIOUSLY? I SHOULD&amp;rsquo;VE KNOWN YOU&amp;rsquo;D ATTACK MY NEW NAME LIKE THAT DAMIAN! AUGH! EVERYONE IS GIVING ME SUCH A HARD TIME! I THOUGHT I&amp;rsquo;D BE SAFE HERE FOR A FEW DAYS BUT NOOOOO storms out of the kitchen
Dick: head in hands Noooooo&amp;hellip; he was finally calm.
Damian: blink blink Since when is &amp;lsquo;Drake&amp;rsquo; a new name?
Jason: walks into the kitchen loading a tranq gun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010 - Duck Season II</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/010/</guid>
      <description>Damian: So&amp;hellip; Drake, is it?
Tim: Yes. And I&amp;rsquo;m keeping it. Fuck the haters.
Damian: I can respect that sentiment.
Tim: Thanks.
Damian: Did you know ducks are an excellent example of a species with intense sexual competition doing strange things to genitalia? Male ducks have penises that can reach three feet in length. I saw a picture of a duck with this twisted, knotted length of venous tissue dangling behind it and thought it was his intestines so remarkable is the resemblance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>017 - Cycles</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/017/</guid>
      <description>Jason: rushes into the media room and shuts the door, leaning heavily on it Fuck! Guys! It&amp;rsquo;s happened!
Tim: Congratulations. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll make a great father.
Jason: What? No! No, it&amp;rsquo;s worse. They&amp;rsquo;ve synced!
Dick: Um, what?
Damian: Tt. Clearly Jason is referring to the menstruation cycles of the women in this household.
Everyone: stares at Damian who pulls out his smart phone
Damian: I&amp;rsquo;ve been tracking their cycles for months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>018 - Welcome Home</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/018/</guid>
      <description>Dick: Tim! You brought your bags! Are you staying at the Manor? Here, let me help you with that it looks heavy!
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Tim: Meh. I sorta got shot up and Alfred said he&amp;rsquo;ll worry himself into an early grave if I&amp;rsquo;m not here where he can keep an eye on me.
Dick: Haha! That sounds like Alfred, alright.
Damian: &amp;hellip;
Tim: And I heard Damian has laryngitis so it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to visit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>020 - Untitled Batfam</title>
      <link>https://moosefrog.com/020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:14:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moosefrog.com/020/</guid>
      <description>Jason: Steal his keys!
Damian: Haha! Then honk until he gets confused!
Tim: No! I&amp;rsquo;m putting his keys in the pond! Ha! No more keys for joo!
Damian: HAHA YES! YES! No more keys for you, oppressive gardener!
Jason: Gimme a turn, Nerd boy!
Tim: Nuh-uh, you know the rule! I play until I die then someone else gets to play!
Damian: Yes, Todd, that is the rule we all agreed to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
